websiteclosers.com 2015-12-16

# Privacy Policy |

Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to Website Closers, LLC (“Company”). This privacy policy provides information about the personal information that Company collects, and the ways in which Company uses that personal information.

**Personal information collection**  
Company automatically receives and records non-personal information on server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information and the page you requested. Company may use this information to customize the content you see. However, Company does not connect this non-personal data to any personal information collected from you. Company also allows third party companies that are presenting advertisement on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Again, these cookies are not connected to any personal information. Third party cookie usage is subject to their own privacy policy, and Company assumes no responsibility or liability for this usage. Company may also collect and use the following kinds of personal information:

  * information about your use of this website
  * information that you provide when contacting us
  * information about transactions carried out over this website; and any other information that you send to Company.

**What we do with the information we gather**  
We require this information to understand your needs and to provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping.
  * to improve our products and services.
  * We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website.
  * administer this website.
  * personalize the website for you.
  * enable your access to and use of the website services.
  * publish information about you on the website; and
  * send you marketing communications.

Where Company discloses your personal information to its agents or sub-contractors for these purposes, the agent or sub-contractor in question will be obligated to use that personal information in accordance with the terms of this privacy policy. In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere above, Company may disclose your personal information to the extent that it is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise or defend its legal rights.

**Securing your data**  
Company will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information when compared to similar websites providing similar content.

**Cross-border data transfers**  
Information that Company collects may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which Company operates to enable the use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy. In addition, personal information that you submit for publication on the website will be published on the internet and may be available around the world. You agree to such cross-border transfers of personal information.

**Updating this statement**  
Company may update this privacy policy by posting a new version on this website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with any changes.

**Other websites**  
This website contains links to other websites. Company is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third party.

**Consent**  
If you do not consent to the collection, use or disclosure of your personal information as outlined in this policy, please do not provide any personal information to Company. If you have provided personal information to Company and no longer consent to its use or disclosure as outlined herein, please contact us in writing.

**Security**  
Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be considered 100% secure, so please keep this in mind when transmitting data to us. Company retains your personal information only as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes identified above or as required by law.

**Results**

We connect our Sale Side Clients with the right Buyers to ensure a quick sale and to maximize clients’ profits. When selling your business you have 2 ...

**Strategies**

After two decades in the ecommerce broker business, we are able to use our extensive experience to devise multiple strategies to the assets being ...

**Services**

WebsiteClosers.com is comprised of a knowledgeable and ...

**Deal Financing**

Every business acquisition is different, which means the methods used to acquire each and every business, might have its own set of factors to make ...

## Seller Consultation

We offer a FREE Seller Consultation, so it costs you nothing upfront to learn what we can do for you. We encourage you to give us a call, talk to our team, and we will prove that we have the experience, skills and drive to sell your business using our professional sales strategies.

  * 14Dec

## [Increase Your Social Media Traffic](http://www.websiteclosers.com/increase-your-social-media-traffic/)

Social media is relatively new, of course, and you want to make the most of it with your blog content and twitter ...

  * 4Dec

## [Increase Your Website Value by Increasing the Power of Personal Connections](http://www.websiteclosers.com/increase-your-website-value-by-increasing-the-power-of-personal-connections/)

Sure, the internet is worldwide, which means you’ll never, ever, meet all of your customers. But what about the ...

  *
